（忆往昔）
- 鲁弗斯·特纳是猎魔人 - 是你的老友吗
- Rufus Turner is a hunter. - One of your old friends?
太好了 你在家
Oh, good. You're home.
听着 你得帮我埋个尸体
Listen, you got to help me bury a body.
就是萨穆埃尔一直在做的事
It's just something Samuel's been doing.
抓住它们 带到某处
Catching things, taking them somewhere,
盘问信息
grilling them for info.
盘问
Grill.
你是说折磨吧
Torture, right?
你出卖了我们
You sold us out?
对我来说你到底算是个什么
What exactly are you supposed to be to me?
我来告诉你我算什么
I'll tell you who I am.
我是个你再也不想见到的人
I'm the guy you never want to see again.
下一次你见到我
The next time you see me,
我会杀了你
I'll be there to kill you.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hi.
格温·坎贝尔 第三代表妹
Gwen campbell. Third cousin.
他们的成长经历 跟我们一样
They grew up in the life, like us.
我想你们应该知道「炼狱」
I'm thinking you know "Purgatory".
为了开门让什么东西进来
This is all about opening a door to let something in.
- 是什么 - 我还在研究
- What? - I'm working on it.
能给点提示吗
Could you give us something?
有个名字 「万物之母」
I got a name."Mother of all".
我们有很多事要做
We have so much to do.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
（如今）
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我吓到你了吗
Did I scare you?
你没事吧
You okay?
你看上去有点
You look a little …
我想搭个便车
Well, I could use a ride.
好吧
Okay.
甜心 你叫什么名字
So, what's your name, sweetheart?
- 夏娃 - 夏娃 我叫里克
- Eve. - Eve. I'm Rick.
你要去多远的地方 夏娃
So, how far you going, Eve?
你想要多远就多远
However far you want.
夏娃
Whoa, whoa. Eve.
听着 你很漂亮
Look, you're very pretty,
但你这样做不对
but this is not what's right for you.
相信我
Trust me.
那我怎样做才是对的
Then what's right for me?
（耶稣爱你）
你内心的空虚
This emptiness you feel inside …
是渴望得到他的关爱
It's really a hunger for him.
你知道其实耶稣只是个普通人
You do know that Jesus was just a man.
当然 但他也是上帝之子
Sure, but he was also the son of god,
上帝爱我们 所以派耶稣降临尘世
sent here because he loves us.
上帝才不关心你们呢
God doesn't care about you.
他当然关心我们
Sure he does.
你的父亲创造了你 然后将你抛弃
Your father made you and then abandoned you,
所以你祈祷
so you pray.
你在虚无之中看见神迹
You see signs where there's nothing.
但事实是 你的天启降临然后消失
But truth is, your apocalypse came and went,
你甚至都没有注意到
and you didn't even notice.
一个母亲绝不会像他一样遗弃自己的孩子
A mother would never abandon her children like he did.
你会明白的
You'll see.
明白什么
See what?
我可以和你说个秘密吗
Can I tell you a secret?
[邪恶力量 第6季第16集]
我这周一直收到猎魔人的信息
I've been getting blasts from hunters all week.
吸血鬼的老巢
Nest of vamps.
狼人的舞会
Werewolf dance party.
6个变形怪
Shifters, six of them.
两个猎魔人为了消灭它们牺牲了
Two hunters died taking them out.
食尸鬼 食尸鬼
Ghouls, ghouls.
食尸鬼幽灵自助餐
Ghoul-wraith smorgasbord.
看来是沿着80号洲际高速直线扫荡啊
Is it just me, or is that a straight kick-line down I-80?
正是
Exactly.
看上去好像土豆怪兽版的远征军
Looks to me like it's a Sherman March monster mash.
是的 但他们要去哪里
Yeah, but where are they marching to?
是啥
What is it?
有个人锤烂了家人的脑袋
Guy bashes in his family's heads.
正如我对警察说的
It's like I told the cops.
我昏过去了
I blacked out.
告诉我们你还记得什么
Well, just tell us what you do remember.
我行驶在日常路线上
Driving my regular route,
然后在我的卡车里醒来 而且在工作的地方
and then I-I woke up in my truck at work.
你在哪工作
And where's work?
星光罐头厂
Starlight cannery.
我不记得自己怎么到那里去的
I-I didn't remember how I got there…
所以就给家里打了电话
So I called home.
没人接电话
When no one picked up,
我赶回家 发现
I-I went there, and I found…
在你昏迷之前 有没有什么异常现象
Anything unusual before you blacked out?
景象 气味 任何不寻常的事情
Sights, smells, anything off the routine?
没有 普通的夜晚
No. Basic night.
在卡车站 我让某个孩子搭了便车
I was giving some kid from the truck stop a ride.
她走了
She took off.
我想她走了
I-I think she took off.
还有什么
Anything else?
我发誓 我不是有意的
I swear … I didn't mean to do it.
我爱他们
I-I loved them.
那么 恶魔附身或者幽灵
So, demon possession or ghosts?
我以为这事和怪物有关
I thought this was a monster thing.
好的 看看吧
All right, here we go.
卡车站 杀人夜
Truck stop, night of the murders.
那是他
That's him.
美女哟
Hmm. Hello.
- 我嘞个去 这是啥玩意 - 鲍比
- Freakish nightmare. What the hell was that? - Bobby?
我从未见过这东西
I've never seen that in my life.
80号洲际公路上的那些吸血鬼和食尸鬼
All those vamps and ghouls out on I-80 …
也许是为了母亲节而来
Maybe they're coming in for mother's day.
好吧 如果她是那个妈咪大佬
Okay, well, if that is big mama …
不管她是什么
Whatever she is,
我们都不知道怎样猎杀她
We got zero on ganking her.
如果遇见她 我们怎么办 期待撒盐有用
So what are we gonna do if we run into her? Throw salt and hope?
不 我们夹尾巴开溜
No, we're gonna turn tail and run,
因为我们已经无计可施了
because we're in over our heads.
我是说 我们要在碰到那骚娘们之前
I mean, we better get some real info on this bitch…
找到点关于她的资料
…before we do run into her.
我们走
Hey, let's go.
怎么回事
What's the ruckus?
罐头工厂有个人崩溃发狂了
A guy just went postal down at the cannery.
我去 你们继续查
Okay, I'll go. You finish here.
联邦探员 威利斯
FBI. Willis.
- 里边有多少 - 死了六个
- How many in there? - Six dead.
- 怎么回事 - 一个人走进去
- What happened? - Apparently, a guy walks in,
拿出猎枪 直接就开火了
pulls a hunting rifle, just opens fire.
队长 这是探员
Captain! This is agent …
怎么 城里在开联邦大会什么的吗
What? There a fed convention in town or something?
你说什么
I beg your pardon.
威利斯探员
Agent willis?
我没认错吧
Am I right?
探员
Agent.
我倒是没想到你会来
I wasn't expecting you…yet.
显然 你没接到我电话
Well, apparently, you didn't get the call.
先生们 我们失陪下
Gentlemen, can you excuse us?
你在这里搞什么 鲁弗斯
What in the high holy are you doing here, Rufus?
和你一样 追踪各种疯狂事件
Same as you … tracking 31 flavors of crazy,
结果我们都查到这儿来了
which led us both smack into the middle of this.
好吧
Right.
我们能和犯人谈谈吗
Can we talk to the perp?
我们可以试试
Well, we can give it a shot.
不过 不知道他能不能回答我们
I don't know if he's gonna talk back to us, though.
警察打中了他八枪
Cops put eight bullets in him.
那么
So…
干嘛
So what?
那么咱们一起办这案子吗
So are we partnering on this or not?
拜托 这有很难吗
Come on, man. It's not rocket surgery.
既然都在 合作一把呗
We're here. Let's do this.
就像以前一样
Just like old times.
车要我来开
Long as I get to drive.
当然不行
Hell no.
你觉得那什么之母
So, do you think the mother of whatever the hell.
专爱搞这个吗 鲍比
is wrapped up in this, Bobby?
看起来像
Looks like.
这些人只是疯了 鲍比
These are just guys going berserk, bobby.
有什么可惊奇的
How is that a monster thing?
我不知道 所以要把他切开看看
I don't know. That's why we're hacking him open.
把那边的棉签给我拿来
Hand me one of those swab things over there.
发现什么了
What have you got?
外胚层吗
That ecto?
不是外胚层
That's not ecto.
这什么玩意
What the hell is that?
是新东西
It's something new.
新的 没什么东西是新的 鲍比
New? No such thing as new, Bobby.
反正不太正常
Well, it's something.
那些忽然发疯的人
Those guys who snapped,
唯一的共同点就是
one thing they had in common …
他们都在罐头厂工作
They both worked at that cannery joint.
你怎么可能考到驾照
I don't even know why you have a driver's license.
看俺们鲍叔把谁带来了
well, look what the cat dragged in.
很高兴见到你 鲁弗斯
It really is good to see you, Rufus.
我看也是
I can believe it.
你们肯定烦死了
It must get old.
老得自己对付这悲催货
dealing with this miserable cuss here all by yourself.
这都被你看出来了
Is it that obvious?
你们仨开房去得了
Why don't you three get a room?
好吧 东西带齐了不
All right, we all pack a snack?
去看看情况吧
Let's see what we can see.
- 格温 - 迪恩
- Gwen? - Dean.
又见面了
Welcome to next time.
别 别 别 慢着
No, no, no, no! Hold on!
- 我说了会杀他 - 等一会
- I said I'd kill him! - Look, just a second.
我想你们认识对方
I take it you know each other.
他是我们的祖父
He's our grandfather.
有人要拥抱喽
Somebody needs a hug.
你在这里做什么
Why are you here?
工作 你们呢
We're working. You?
不关你丫的事
None of your damn business!
萨姆 带迪恩出去走走
Sam, take Dean for a walk.
- 你搞笑呢 - 迪恩 没事的
- You got to be kidding me. - Look, Dean, it's fine.
怎么可能
How?
- 你怎么回事 - 他可能知道些什么
- What is wrong with you? - Look, maybe he knows something.
你不记得他做过什么 我记得
You don't remember what he did. I do.
我知道
I know.
我没想阻止你 我叫你等下
I'm not saying don't. I'm saying not yet.
那么 你就是萨穆埃尔
So…You're Samuel.
那你就是扮演他们父亲的那个人了
You must be the guy pretending to be their father.
总得有人罩着他们
Well, somebody ought to.
萨姆
Sam.
你看起来不错
You're looking well.
别说闲话了 好吗
Save the small talk, all right?
你看起来不一样了
You seem different.
我拿回了我的灵魂
I got my soul back.
听说 你屁忙都没帮
No thanks to you, I hear.
你听说
You hear?
你不记得了
You don't remember.
该记得的我可没忘
I remember enough.
很抱歉打断这有爱的氛围
I, uh, really hate to break up this little circle of love,
但是我们能不能回到正题
But why don't we talk shop, huh?
不如跟我们说说你在猎杀什么
How about you tell us what it is you're hunting?
炼狱的一个生物
A creature from purgatory.
她自称夏娃
She calls herself Eve.
- 夏娃 - 是的
- Eve? - Yep.
它们叫她母亲
They call her mother.
她一万年前就存在了
She was here about 10, 000 years ago.
地球上每一个活生生的怪物
Every freak that walks the face of the earth.
都能追溯到她那里
can be traced back to her.
现在她回来了
And she's back.
你怎么知道这些的
How the hell do you know all that?
我吃的盐比你吃的米还多 孩子
You don't know half the things that I know, kid.
直到最近 你才知道我们的存在
Hell, until recently, you didn't even know about us.
我知道你把自己的家人丢给饥饿的食尸鬼
I now know that you'd throw your own kin to hungry ghouls.
知道这些就够了
I think I know enough.
你做了什么
You what?
迪恩对他撒谎
Dean lied to the man.
你何不问问迪恩
How about you ask Dean?
好主意
Good idea.
迪恩
Dean.
那是真的么
Is it true?
什么
What?
萨穆埃尔有没有曾试图…
Did Samuel really try to …
弄死我吗 有
Kill me? Yes.
连眼都不带眨的
He didn't even blink.
跟你合伙的 就是这么个人
That's the guy you're rolling with.
那件事他一点都没说过
He didn't tell me anything about that.
我不知道的
I didn't know.
我知道
I know.
其实 我要告诉你一些事情
Honestly, there's something I need to tell you.
什么事
What?
先试着把伤口堵住 鲍比
See if you can plug that hole up, Bobby.
挺住 姑娘
Come on, girl!
挺住
Come on!
醒醒
她不行了
She's gone.
妈的
Ah, damn it.
很遗憾 如果你在意的话
I'm sorry…If you care.
去你妈的 我当然在意
Screw you. I care.
她是不是
Is she, uh…
- 迪恩呢 - 没找到
- Where's Dean? - I couldn't find him.
迪恩肯定被附身了 跟那些人一样
Whatever got into those guys must have got into Dean.
鲁弗斯 帮萨穆埃尔把她挪走
Rufus, help Samuel move her somewhere.
我跟萨姆把这儿锁起来
Sam and I will lock down here.
我们得在迪恩找上我们前 先找到他
We're gonna want to find Dean before he finds us.
我们要的是活口 萨穆埃尔
We're gonna find him alive, Samuel,
不然我就一枪打爆你的头
Or I'm gonna put a bullet into your head.
迪恩 你他妈把抢放下
Dean, put that damn thing down.
迪恩 放下
Dean, put it down.
放倒你简直轻而易举 鲁弗斯
You're the least of my worries right now, Rufus.
喂喂 你们俩都冷静
Hey, hey, hey. Okay, both of you.
- 俩你妹 - 没心情跟你逗贫
- Both of us, my ass. - I'm not in the mood.
刚有一个12英寸的疱疹从我耳朵里爬出去
I just had a 12-inch…herpe crawl out of my ear.
- 啥 - 你听见了
- What? - You heard me.
我醒来 躺在地上
I just woke up on the ground,
刚好看见这…蠕虫似的东西
just in time to see this … this…worm thing.
他妈的从我耳朵里出来 爬那通风口里去了
sliding out of my freaking ear and into that vent.
你们说这是怎么回事
So you tell me what the hell's going on!
你杀了格温 就这么回事
You killed Gwen. That's what's going on.
我们只是在走廊里说话
We were just talking out in the hallway.
这是我记得的最后一件事
That's the last thing I remember.
那东西肯定是上我身了
That thing must have jumped me.
那就是说 有个怪物附在了你身上吗
So, we're talking about, like, a monster that gets in you?
那是个超大的肉虫王
It's like a khan worm on steroids.
是说像寄生虫一样 有东西占领了你的身体
You mean like a parasite, something that took over your body.
虫子爬进来 又爬出去了
Worm crawls in you, worm crawls out.
怪物附身吗 这倒新鲜了
Monster possession? That's novel.
或许那东西还在你身体里
Or that thing's still in you,
我们不能相信你的话
and we can't trust a word that you're saying.
没在
It's not!
检查你的耳朵
Check your ear.
什么叫检查我耳朵
What do you mean, check my ear?
检查啥
Check my ear for what?
喂 啥
Hey! What?
想摸我也该先请我喝杯酒吧
Why don't you buy me a drink first?
第二次了 是粘液 没错
Second date. Oh, yeah, we're goo positive.
什么意思 他什么意思
What does that mean? What does that mean?
意思是 那东西确实进去过
That means it was in you, all right.
- 或者说是一直在 - 没在我身上
- Or it still is. - It's not in me!
好了
Okay.
- 各位都把枪交出来 - 什么
- Everybody, give up your guns. - What?
喂喂 好好想想 鲍比
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, think about this for a second, Bobby.
我想 我们都不知道究竟谁
I'm thinking we don't know who is and who ain't got.
被那可恶的肉虫王附身了
the damn khan worm up inside his melon.
没在我身上
It's not in me!
我没说在你身上
I didn't say it was.
关键是 我们不知道在谁身上
Point is we don't know who it is.
谁都有可能
It could be any one of us.
所以我们能做的 就是尽量别让那东西
So the best we can do… Is to make it that much harder.
搞得咱们互相爆头
for that thing to blow our fool heads off.
等着给你下请柬呐 坎贝尔
Are you waiting for a handwritten invite, Campbell?
好了
Okay.
我们得喘口气 计划一下
We need some time to breathe, make a plan.
计划
A plan?
靠什么计划
Based on?
我要打几个电话
I'm gonna make a few phone calls,
看看有没有人听说过这东西
see if anybody ever heard of anything like this.
嗯 我也来
Hmm. Ditto.
我这边也有点门路
Got a few trees I can shake.
扯淡呢 阿拉德
Oh, balls, Allard.
不 我跟你说了
No, I told you that.
妈的
Damn it.
别紧张
Relax.
上个厕所
Bathroom break.
除非你想帮我拿着…
So unless you want to hold it for me…
操 狗屁都没查到
Well, I got a dump truck full of bubkes.
我也是 你给威利打过吗
Nothing here, either. You call Willie?
当然了 你当我傻啊
Of course. Think I'm an idjit?
罗杰呢
How about Rodge?
他不跟我说话
Wouldn't talk to me.
嗯 他也不理我
Yeah, me neither.
好吧 备选计划
Okay, plan "B."
咱直接把那东西揪出来吧
Let's just go and grab the thing.
之后怎么办
And then what, exactly?
我们要么滚蛋 要么火拼
Well, we sit on our thumbs, or we go in guns blazing.
跟奥马哈似的吗
Like Omaha?
跟你说
You know what?
去你妈的 说什么奥马哈
Screw you for bringing up Omaha.
太三俗了
That's just low.
要干嘛
What?
没啥 我只是很好奇
Nothing. I'm just.
你晚上睡得怎么样
wondering how you sleep at night.
像婴儿般熟睡 谢谢关心
Like a baby. Thanks for asking.
你把我们俩献给克劳力
You fed us to Crowley.
没错 但现在说这些也没用了
True, but what am I gonna do about it now?
我应该责怪你想要杀死我吗
Do I blame you for wanting to kill me?
迪恩 当然不
Of course not, Dean.
我所做的一切都是…
What I did was…
我是不会道歉的
But I'm not apologizing.
我敢作敢当 不会纠结已经发生的事
I did what I did. I don't cry over spilled blood.
你就这么心安理得么
So you really can just go on, like…
虽然你现在把灵魂找回来了
Just because you're Dr. Jekyll at the moment,
也不代表你可以这么趾高气扬
doesn't mean you can get all high and mighty.
别忘了 咱俩可相处了一年
Don't forget, we spent a year together.
是的 我们是亲人
Yeah, we did. We're blood.
但是你仍然出卖了我
And you still sold me out.
相信我 跟你比起来
Trust me, what I did pales.
我做的那些事就是小巫见大巫
in comparison to what you did,
而且还不止一次
and on more than one occasion.
那好 告诉我我都干过什么
All right, tell me what I did.
萨姆 不行 别这样
No. Sam, come on.
你之所以现在还活着
The only reason you're alive right now.
是因为我们还有正事要办
is because we're working a job.
一旦我们杀掉这个怪物 你是下一个
The minute we kill this thing…You're next.
行啊
Okay, then.
我们走着瞧
We'll just see.
我听到枪声
I heard a shot.
是萨穆埃尔
Samuel!
鲍比 我需要把我的枪拿回来
I'm gonna be needing my gun back now, Bobby.
- 那还用说 - 走吧
- You think? - Yeah.
喂 别不开心
Hey, don't feel bad.
这计划不错
You know, it was a good plan,
只不过一个怪物绝对不会
except for the part where a monster would definitely,
乖乖交出他全部的武器
definitely not give up all his weapons.
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
跟丢了
We lost him.
- 有什么计划 - 我们一起行动
- So, what's the plan? - We stick together.
我们得继续找这个怪物 被它附身的人
We got to keep track of this thing, who it's in.
等一下 看这个
Hold on. Look.
是饵雷
Booby trap.
我嘞个去
I'll be damned.
迪恩
Dean!
萨姆
Sam!
糟糕
Damn it.
太贱了
Son of a bitch.
- 迪恩 - 萨姆
- Dean? - Sam!
我在周围转转
I'm gonna go around, okay?
好吧 小心点
All right. Watch yourself.
好
Yeah.
走吧
Come on.
别动
Don't move.
萨姆
Sam.
把枪放下
Put your gun down.
孩子 你想干什么
What you gonna do, son?
你不会对我开枪的
You're not gonna shoot me.
你找回了你的灵魂
You got your soul back.
你会对你的家人开枪吗
You gonna shoot your own family?
是的 我才不管家人什么的
Yeah, I wouldn't go with the family thing.
试试别的
Try again.
玛丽仍然是我的女儿
Mary's still my daughter.
我让你别动
I said don't move.
你的名字也是照我名字取的
You're still named after me.
我让你别动
I said don't move!
萨姆 看来现在就咱俩了
Appears to be our moment, Sam.
还想知道你的暑假是怎么过的吗
You still want to know about your summer vacation?
我会一五一十的告诉你
I'll tell you all about it.
你非常想知道 不是吗
You're dying to know, huh?
是 没错
Yeah, I am.
那咱就把枪放下 好好谈谈
Well, then, let's just put these down and talk.
- 别动 - 没事的 萨姆
- Stop. - It's all right, Sam.
萨姆
Sam.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
萨姆 把枪放下
Drop the gun, Sam.
是我
It's me.
好吧
Okay.
萨姆 很好
That's great, Sam.
但在我们确定之前先要铐住你
Just got to cuff you, uh, till we can be sure, okay?
你理解的吧
You understand, right?
那东西在他身体里
It's in him.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的 是的
Yeah. Yeah, I think.
在他倒下之后
You see anything come out of him…
你有没有看到什么东西出来
after he dropped?
你最好是有所发现
Tell me you got something.
什么也没有
Nothing.
啥
What?
你是说我杀他的时候 他不是怪物
So … so you mean he wasn't a monster when I ganked him?
有一种方法能确认
One way to find out.
鲍比 你车里有能切颅骨的锯吗
Bobby, you got a cranial saw in the car?
当然有了
Of course.
你不能自己去
You're not going alone.
不不 他不是自己去
Oh, no, he won't. He won't.
我们俩一起去拿些工具
We will both go grab some tools.
看能不能接通这里的电源
and see about getting some power in this place.
而你们俩
And I want you and you to …
我需要你和你看着他和他
Okay, I want you and you to watch him and him and …
如果有任何东西从谁的身体里爬出来
All right, if anything crawls out of anybody,
要有人赶紧搞定它
somebody step on it.
行 不用担心 我会看着萨穆埃尔
Yeah, don't worry. I'll watch Samuel.
迪恩会看着我
Dean will watch me.
行 就这样
Yeah, all right.
你做的没错
You did the right thing, you know.
你是说你觉得我做的对
You mean you think I did,
如果他确实被附身 而且我没有
if it's in him and I'm me.
我们就像在玩三赌一的游戏
This thing's playing three-card monte with us.
我猜你还是你吧
Well, I'm just gonna assume you're you.
那你能帮我把这个松开吗
You want to take this off, then?
那要等我们把那东西从他脑子里弄出来
Not till we get that sucker out of his walnut.
我也不知道
I don't know.
我几乎不记得他了
I mean, I barely remember him,
而我记得的那些事 很不好
and what I do remember… it's not good.
他还那样对我们
And what he did to us…
可是
But…
还有「可是」
There's a "But"?
我不停地在想
I mean, I just can't help but think…
妈妈会怎么说
What would mom say?
知道我认为妈会怎么说吗
You know what I think mom would say?
她会说 光有血缘关系不能算是一家人
She'd say just 'cause you're blood doesn't make you family.
亲情是用实际行动换来的
You got to earn that.
好了
Well… all right.
手术开始
Let's play operation.
- 小子们不出去透透气 - 不用
- You boys want to take a breather? - We're good.
我们这是要给你们外公开瓢
We're about to crack open your grandpa's grapefruit.
出去转转
Take a breather.
什么破玩意 你又去翻垃圾堆啦
What is this? Have you been dumpster-diving again?
怎么了 还能用呢
What? It still works.
好吧 随你
Yeah, right.
希望能用
Hope so.
鲁弗斯 我一直在想
Listen, Rufus, I've been thinking.
这些破事还有完没完
Yeah, will wonders never cease?
你消停一会儿 我有话要说
Yeah, s-shut up a minute. I'm trying to say something.
奥马哈那事是我的错
It was my fault … Omaha.
不 不是
No. No, it wasn't.
是我的错 我当时应该听你的
No, I should … I should have listened to you.
鲍比 听我的那是必须的
Well, hey, that's categorical, Bobby.
让我 让我把话说出来
I … l-let me just get this out.
鲍比 这事早说过了
Bobby, we've had this conversation already, okay?
不 没有 鲁弗斯 我一直没道歉
No, we haven't. I never said I'm sorry, Rufus.
因为我你才失去了她 我…
I … you lost her because of me, and I…
鲍比 我说这事不用再说了
Bobby, I said we've had this conversation already.
你就是啰嗦上一天也没用 鲍比
And you could blabber all day… and it wouldn't change a thing, Bobby.
发生那些事 我永远不会原谅你
I will never forgive you for what happened.
懂了吗
You got that?
永远
Never.
换个话题吧 鲍比
So change the subject, Bob.
- 鲍比 你怎么样 - 鲁弗斯
- Bobby, you okay? - Rufus.
你没事吧
Hey, you all right?
醒醒
Wake up.
没事了 我扶你
It's all right. I got you.
起来
Come on.
你们仨都在 看来不是我的来生
This can't be my afterlife 'cause the three of you are here.
发生什么事了
What happened?
我们走的时候他还在桌上挺尸呢
Well, when we left, he was dead on the table.
没错 后来他诈尸了
Yeah, till he wasn't.
他是怎么死了又死的
So how did he get double dead?
鲍比把他推到开关上
Bobby threw him against that.
我想上面肯定通着电
I guess it was a live wire.
电路短路 他开始抽搐
It shorted, and he went ape.
然后那东西就从他耳朵里爬了出来
Then that thing crawled out of his ear.
至少我们知道它的克星是什么了
At least we know what tickles it.
电
Electricity.
现在的问题是 它到哪儿去了
Yeah. Now the question is, where'd it go?
- 你们看到了吗 - 没
- You see? - No.
- 你们俩有可能被附身 - 对
- You two were down for the count. - Yeah.
它要么是跑了 要么是在你俩谁的身上
Well, either it bailed or it's in either one of you.
又或者 在你们俩身上
Or…It's in one of you.
不对 我们俩刚才都清醒
No, we were awake.
- 你们有盯着对方吗 - 有
- Did you have eyes on each other? - Yes.
一秒都不落吗
100% of the time?
怎样算一秒都不落
Define 100%.
我就说嘛
Like I said.
好吧 那不如我们检查有没有粘液
All right, how about, uh, check for goo, right?
没有
Nothing.
它可能就是跑了
It might just be gone.
不对
No.
它可能是学聪明了掩盖了痕迹
It might have wised up and covered its trail.
好吧 那我们来百分百确认下
All right, let's settle this…100%.
怎么确认
How?
通电了
You're live.
好
Okay.
成了
我不是医生 但我敢说他是死透了
I'm not a doctor, but I'm gonna go ahead and call this one.
好了 谁先来
Yeah. All right, who wants to go first?
- 来吧 - 你确定
- Come on. - You sure?
快点 别等我反…
Hurry up before I start thinking…
王八羔…
Son of a…
爽
Whew. Awesome.
要不要帮你…
Here, you want me to…
给我吧
Let's go.
好
Yep.
不好意思 不好意思
Uh, no, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
躲不了的 鲁弗斯 别磨蹭
No passes, Rufus. Come on.
- 我装着心脏起搏器呢 - 祈祷它质量过关吧
- I got a damn pacemaker. - Well, you better hope it's a good one.
你什么时候装的起搏器
Since when do you got a pacemaker?
小布什第一届任期装的
Since Bush Jr., term one.
哥们还少了三根脚趾 顺便说下
I'm down three toes, too, F.Y.I.
好吧 来吧 痛快点
All right, come on. Just make it quick.
老天
God!
妈的 妈的
Damn it! Damn it!
- 你没事吧 - 我有事
- You okay? - No, I'm not okay.
给我
Give me that.
好
Okay.
该我了
All right, my turn.
它没在我身上 来吧
Well, it ain't inside me, so go right ahead.
鲍比 站着别动
All right, then just stand still, Bobby.
行 当然
Okay, sure.
- 我会很快的 - 没问题
- I'll make this quick. - No problem.
好了吗 来吧
All right? Let's do this.
鲁弗斯 稍等
Okay, uh, just a second, Rufus.
稍等个毛 你个怪物
Just a second nothing, whatever you are.
我是鲍比啊
I'm Bobby.
鲍你大爷
Bobby, my ass.
鲍比
Bobby!
Bobby,
你现在孤军奋战 想单挑我们两个吗
there are two of us and one of you.
你好呀 小疱疹
Well, hey, there, you little herpe.
你为什么总说疱疹呢
Why do you keep talking about herpes?
你说啥
What?
我没有 闭嘴
I don't. Shut up.
闭嘴
Shut up.
听着 想从这里逃出去 门都没有
Now, don't you even think about shagging ass out of here,
屋里的所有缝隙都封住了
'cause we got every crack in this room sealed.
好好享受吧
So get comfy.
我挺舒服
I am comfy.
呆在里面很爽
It's nice in here.
而且你们很爱他 不是吗
And you love this guy, don't you?
你们要杀我 他也躲不过去
You really want to kill me and take him with me?
今天死掉的同伴还不够多吗
Haven't you lost enough pals today?
逼不得已的话也得这么办
We'll do what we have to do.
我们有几个问题问你
And we got some questions for you,
所以你最好好好配合
so you can either play ball,
否则的话就把你烤成干儿
or we could fry up a little shrimp on the barbie.
问吧 早等着你们问呢
Ask. Been waiting for you to ask.
你这是什么意思
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
意思是我没什么可隐瞒的
It means I got nothing to hide.
你是什么
What are you?
到现在还不知道我是什么吧
You haven't got a name for me yet.
我才出现不久
I'm new around here.
夏娃把我造出来的
Eve cooked me up herself.
夏娃这贱人到底是谁
Who is she, this Eve bitch?
我们的母亲
The mother of all of us.
也是你们的末日
And the end of all of you.
等她成功以后
By the time she's done,
怪物会比人类还多
there'll be more creatures than humans.
我们会把你们圈养起来
You'll live in pens.
然后把小孩当做小牛肉做菜吃
We'll serve up your young and call it veal.
那你要怎么做呢
And what's your deal in all of this?
控制几个卡车司机有什么用么
I mean, how's jumping a few truckers gonna help?
你觉得我在这里
You think I'm here.
就为了搞几个罐头厂工人么
to mess with a couple of cannery workers?
是为了引你们过来
We led you here.
为什么
Why?
她让我捎句话给你
She has a message for you.
是吗 什么话
Oh, yeah? What's that?
你们都得死
You're all gonna die.
她非常生气 她就在这里
She's pissed. She's here.
从此刻开始
And it's gonna be nothing but pain.
除了痛苦你们将一无所有
for you from here on in.
那好 我的回复是这个
Well, here's my response.
迪恩
Dean.
Dean!
你觉得他还能坚持多久
How much more do you think he can take?
你们杀不了我 杀了我他就得死
You can't kill me, not without taking him with me.
那好 我们也是迫不得已
Well… We'll just have to do.
但鲍比也会让我们这么做
what Bobby would want us to do.
小鼻涕虫看你怎么出去
No way out now, slug-o.
鲍比 坚持住
Bobby, hang on in there.
鲍比
Bobby?
他不会是
Is he, uh…
醒醒
Hey, hey.
鲍比
Bobby.
鲍比 醒醒
Bobby, hey.
没有呼吸了 鲍比
He's not breathing. Bobby!
我从没觉得鲁弗斯是教徒
I got to say, I never figured Rufus for the religious type.
他不太严格遵守教规
Well, he didn't exactly keep kosher.
每次我们一起埋尸体时
He always used to pull.
他总是用老套的
the old "Can't work on the sabbath" card.
「不能在安息日工作」搪塞我
whenever we had to bury a body.
我曾有份工作
You know, I-I was just a job.
我曾是个默默无闻的技工
I was joe mechanic.
有天我的妻子着魔了
Then my wife got possessed…
她疯了似的要杀我
Went nuts on me.
我刺伤了她 可是没用
I stabbed her, and that didn't stop her.
接下来 这家伙破门而入
Next thing I knew, this guy comes busting in,
用圣水洒了她
soaks her with holy water,
把那恶魔直接送回了地狱
and sends that demon straight to hell so fast.
杀了她之后 我本来想逃得远远的
I'd have gone away for killing her.
可是
But…
鲁弗斯搞定了一切
Rufus cleaned up everything.
教了我一些关于
Taught me a thing or two about…
世间邪恶生物的事
what's really out there.
不久 我们就一起上路
Pretty soon, we were riding together.
一起工作了多年
Worked like that for years,
有点像你们两兄弟
Kind of like you two knuckleheads.
后来发生什么事了
So, what happened?
因为奥马哈的事
It was Omaha.
都是我的错
It was my fault.
而且他从没能原谅我
And he never let it go.
他应该原谅你的
Well, he should have.
你不知道我都做了什么 迪恩
You don't know what I did, dean.
没关系的
Doesn't matter.
你什么意思 怎么就没关系
What do you mean, it doesn't …
我是说 到头来 你们还是亲如兄弟
I mean at the end of the day, you two are family.
生命很短暂 而我们的更短
Life's short, and ours are shorter than most.
生命不是用来提心吊胆惴惴不安的
We're gonna spend it wringing our hands?
总有一天 我们会死在什么妖魔鬼怪的手下
Something's gonna get us eventually,
当我小命要玩儿完的时候
and when my guts get ripped out,
我可先告诉你们 我们依然是一家人
just so you two know, we're good.
那些不管是谁犯下的错
Blanket apology for all the crap.
一切都没关系
that anybody's done all the way around.
今天话很多啊 迪恩
Some of us pulled a lot of crap, Dean.
过去的一笔勾销
Well, clean slate.
好吧
Okay.